Finding Aid for the Julian Goodman Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Julian Goodman Papers
undated
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0880
Biographical Note:
Personal Life
Julian Goodman was born on May 1st, 1922 in Glasgow, Kentucky to parents Clara Franklin and Charles Austin Goodman, Sr. He was the youngest of three sons. From 1939-1942 Goodman attended Western Kentucky University (then Western State College). His time there was interrupted by a brief career in the army from 1942-1943. Upon return, Goodman began working a government research job in Washington, DC and earned his Bachelor’s degree in Economics at George Washington University in 1948. Goodman married Betty Davis, also a Kentucky native, in 1946. The couple had four children: Julie, John, Jeffrey, and Greg.
Career
Goodman’s successful journalism career famously began on a three dollar per week salary at The Glasgow Daily Times. Later, Goodman took a government research job for the Combined Production and Resources Board in Washington, DC. While there, Goodman met William McAndrew, the head of NBC News. McAndrew hired Goodman as a news writer for WRC, NBC’s Washington news outlet in 1945. Over the next twenty years Goodman became a key player for NBC, quickly moving up the ranks. In 1956 he hired Chet Huntley and David Brinkley to head the reports for that year’s political conventions. Huntley and Brinkley’s reporting was very successful, and Goodman gave them an evening news program: the Huntley – Brinkley Report. The program became NBC’s flagship evening news program, running from 1956-1970. Goodman considered pairing the two reporters one of the best moments in his career. In 1959, Goodman was named Director of NBC News and Public Affairs. In this position, he produced the “Great Debates” between future Presidents John F. Kennedy and Richard Nixon. Goodman then became Vice President of NBC News in 1961 and Senior Executive Vice President of Operations, Executive Vice President, and Senior Vice president all in 1965. In 1966 Goodman was elected President and Chief Administrative Officer of NBC. At age 44, he was NBC’s youngest president and one of the first to come through broadcasting rather than sales, which marked a change in the way the broadcasting world did business. He served as President of NBC from March 1966 – April 1974.
During his tenure as President, Goodman negotiated a million dollar deal to keep Johnny Carson as host of “The Tonight Show.” He was also at the forefront during the famous debacle now known as the “Heidi Bowl” in which East Coast viewers missed an exciting last minute comeback in a rivalry football game when NBC began showing the movie Heidi at its scheduled time. Goodman is also known for his strong support of First Amendment rights. His outspokenness on the issue landed him on President Nixon’s “opponents list” which was published in newspapers in 1973. Goodman is also famously known for never seeking a raise throughout his career and did not describe himself as an ambitious man. In the years of Goodman’s presidency NBC received over 800 broadcasting awards.
From April 1974 – May 1979 Goodman was Chairman of NBC. At the time of his retirement, he was Chairman of NBC’s Executive Committee.
Goodman was the recipient of numerous broadcasting awards. Among these are the “George Foster Peabody award” for outstanding work in the area of First Amendment Rights and privileges for broadcasting (1974), and, perhaps the most prestigious award in broadcasting, the National Association of Broadcaster’s Distinguished Service Award (1976).
Retirement
On May 31st, 1979 Goodman took an early retirement from NBC, but continued to serve the Board of Directors. In the years after his retirement Goodman joined the Board of Directors for Gannett Inc., a media and marketing solutions company; Gulf Oil Corporation; McDonnell Douglas Corporation, and the Larchmont New York Federal Savings and Loan Association, and was active in other civic, business, and journalistic endeavors. He continued his advocacy for First Amendment rights and in 1987 made a statement before the House Committee against the Fairness Doctrine, legislation which he felt would restrict that right. In 1988 Julian and his wife Betty moved from New York to Florida, where they lived together until his death from kidney failure in July, 2012. During a 1998 interview with the Archive of American Television, Goodman was asked how he would like to be remembered. He answered, “As everybody would like to be remembered. Well and favorably. He did a good job. He did the best he could.”
Chronology/Timeline:
May 1, 1922 Born in Glasgow, Kentucky
1936-1939 Attends and graduates from Glasgow High School in Glasgow, KY
1939- 1942 Begins an A.B. program at Western State College (now Western Kentucky University)
1942 – 1943 Military service
1943 – 1945 Works for the Combined Production and Resources Board in Washington
1945 -1948 Attends and graduates from George Washington University night school with an A.B. in Economics
1945 – 1948 Begins career at NBC as a news writer for station WRC in Washington
1948 – 1950 Washington editor of NBC’s News of the World
1950 – 1959 Manager of News and Special Events for NBC Radio Network and NBC Washington
1956 Supervises NBC’s central news desk at the year’s political conventions; assigns Chet Huntley and David Brinkley to head the reports
1956 – 1970 the Huntley – Brinkley Report begins and airs
1959 – 1961 Director for NBC News and Public Affairs
1960 Produces the “Great Debates” between John. F. Kennedy and Richard Nixon
1961 – 1965 Vice President of NBC News
1965 – 1966 Senior Executive Vice President of Operations of NBC
April 1966 – 1974 President and Chief Administrative Officer of NBC
January 1966 Receives a spot with the Board of Directors of NBC
March 1968 Calls for freedom from legislation and government regulation that tends to “suppress the progressive forces of broadcasting and limit what it can do for the public.”
1970 Named “Kentuckian of the Year”
1971 Becomes one of the names listed in Nixon’s Enemies List
1972 Elected to the Board of Directors of RCA Corporation on January 1, 1972
April 1974 Becomes Chairman of the Board of NBC
October 8, 1978 Becomes Chairman of the NBC Executive Committee
May 31, 1979 Takes an early retirement from NBC
1980 Joins the Board of Directors of Gannett Inc.
July 1981 Gulf Oil Corporation elects Goodman to its Board of Directors
1987 Makes a statement before the House Committee, stating strong disapproval of the Fairness Doctrine.
July 2012 Death of Julian Goodman in Florida.
Scope and Content Note:
This collection is comprised of the personal and corporate papers including photographs, audio visual material, and memorabilia of Julian Goodman who was both President and Chairman of the Board of NBC (the National Broadcasting Company) from 1966 until his retirement in May of 1979. The dates of these papers range from 1941 - 1996, with the majority of the material in the 34 year period that Goodman worked for NBC ( 1945 - 1979).
The collection is comprised of approximately 65 linear feet of material and is arranged in the following series:
Personal and Biographical
Articles/Congressional Testimony/Speeches by Julian Goodman
NBC Corporate Affiliates
NBC Corporate People
NBC Corporate Personal
NBC Corporate Programming
NBC Corporate RCA
NBC Corporate Reports
NBC Corporate Subject Files
NBC Corporate U.S. Government
Gannett Corporation Board
Photographs
Audio Visual Materials
Memorabilia
Oversize
Although there is not a Correspondence Series per se, the bulk of the material in one way or another is heavily weighted with Goodman’s letters, memos, and written comments and notes and with incoming memos, letters, reports, and notes from his colleagues and other associates with whom he conducted the business of this major U.S. broadcasting corporation on a daily basis. Prominent among the correspondents are David Brinkley, Robert Kintner, David Adams, Reuven Frank, Walter D. Scott, and William McAndrews.
- Personal and Biographical
  - Activities and Organizations
    - Academy of Television Arts and Sciences – Hall of Fame Selection Committee, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 1.)
    - American Council for the Arts – Benefit Co-Chair, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 2.)
    - American Council for the Arts – Benefit Co-Chair, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 3.)
    - Bay Hill (Box 1, Folder 4.)
    - Boards – Associated Press Dinner to honor JG, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 5.)
    - Boards – The Board Room (Private Club) (Box 1, Folder 6.)
    - Boards – Boy Scouts of America, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 7.)
    - Boards – Center for Communication (Box 1, Folder 8.)
    - Boards – Corporate Childcare information (Box 1, Folder 9.)
    - Boards – The George Washington University International Communication Institute (Box 1, Folder 10.)
    - Boards – The George Washington University International Communication Institute (Box 1, Folder 11.)
    - Boards – The George Washington University International Communication Institute (Box 1, Folder 12.)
    - Boards – The George Washington University International Communication Institute (Box 1, Folder 13.)
    - Boards – Gulf Oil Corporation (Box 1, Folder 14.)
    - Boards – Gulf Oil Corporation/Paul Sheldon (Box 1, Folder 15.)
    - Boards – The Kentuckians (Box 1, Folder 16.)
    - Boards – Larchmont Federal Savings and Loan, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 17.)
    - Boards – McDonnell Douglas, 1988 – 1994 (Box 1, Folder 18.)
    - Boards – National Urban League committee, 1975- 1978 (Box 1, Folder 19.)
    - Boards – University of Georgia School of Journalism (Box 1, Folder 20.)
    - Boards – University of Georgia School of Journalism (Box 1, Folder 21.)
  - Activities and Organizations
    - Boards – University of Georgia School of Journalism (Box 2, Folder 1.)
    - Boards – University of Georgia School of Journalism (Box 2, Folder 2.)
    - Boards – University of Georgia School of Journalism (Box 2, Folder 3.)
    - Boards – miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder 4.)
    - Champion Tuck Awards – panelist, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 5.)
    - Democratic Site Selection Committee, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 6.)
    - The George Washington University Alumni (Box 2, Folder 7.)
    - The George Washington University Program in Radio and Television, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 8.)
    - Golf (Box 2, Folder 9.)
    - Golf (Box 2, Folder 10.)
    - International Institute of Communications, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 11.)
    - International Radio and Television Society 50th Anniversary Dinner Committee, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 12.)
    - Kentuckians of New York – Dinners, 1980-81; 1993 (Box 2, Folder 13.)
    - Memberships and dues, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 14.)
    - Memphis State University – Seminar leader, April 1981 (Box 2, Folder 15.)
    - Museum of Broadcasting – lecture – “Broadcasting’s Fight for Freedom”, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 16.)
    - National Association of Broadcasters Convention –Invitation, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 17.)
    - Requests: Public Understanding of Science Panel; Senate Testimony (Box 2, Folder 18.)
  - Awards
    - List, 1959-1977 (Box 2, Folder 19.)
    - Honorary degrees – list; Citation and Presentation documents from University of Florida, August 25, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 20.)
    - Awards, Committee Memberships, Speeches – List, 1978 -79 (Box 2, Folder 21.)
    - George Washington University Alumni Achievement Award, February 22, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 22.)
    - OBIE from the Orange Bowl Committee, May 2, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 23.)
    - Kentuckian of the Year, November 19, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 24.)
    - NBC Service Awards – program, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 25.)
    - International Radio and Television Society Gold Medal, March 9, 1972/remarks (Box 2, Folder 26.)
    - Distinguished Communications Medal Radio and Television Commission, Southern Baptist Convention, February 8, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 27.)
    - American Association of State Colleges and Universities Distinguished Alumnus Award, November 8, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 28.)
    - Sigma Delta Chi Hall of Fame, May 1975 (Box 2, Folder 29.)
    - Distinguished Kentuckian, October 1975 (Box 2, Folder 30.)
    - George Foster Peabody Award, 1974-75 (1) (Box 2, Folder 31.)
  - Awards
    - George Foster Peabody Award, 1974-75 (2) (Box 3, Folder 1.)
    - George Foster Peabody Award, 1974-75 (3) (Box 3, Folder 2.)
    - George Foster Peabody Award, 1974-75 (4) (Box 3, Folder 3.)
    - Distinguished Service Award, National Association of Broadcasters, March 1976 (Box 3, Folder 4.)
    - IRTS (International Radio and Television Society) Gold Medal Award to NBC, March 18, 1976 accepted by JG (Box 3, Folder 5.)
    - Richard Rodgers Award from the Professional Children’s School, December 12, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 6.)
    - The Commonwealth Award of Distinguished Service, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 7.)
    - Di Gamma Kappa Distinguished Achievement in Broadcasting, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 8.)
    - The Common Wealth Award of Distinguished Service – Invitation, 1988-89 (Box 3, Folder 9.)
    - The Oak Award – Louisville, Kentucky, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 10.)
  - Family
    - Genealogy information, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 11.)
    - Goodman, Betty Sue Davis (wife), 1944 (Box 3, Folder 12.)
    - Goodman, Betty Sue Davis (wife), June 19, 1966; Courier Journal article (Box 3, Folder 13.)
    - Goodman, Betty Sue Davis (wife) (Box 3, Folder 14.)
    - Goodman, Charles Austin (father), letter 1971; obituary February 1972 (Box 3, Folder 15.)
    - Goodman, Charles Austin (father) – death – condolences, February 1972 (Box 3, Folder 16.)
    - Goodman, Charles Austin (father) – death – condolences, February 1972 (Box 3, Folder 17.)
    - Goodman, Charles Austin (father) – death – condolences, February 1972 (Box 3, Folder 18.)
    - Goodman, Charles Austin (father) – death – condolences, February 1972 (Box 3, Folder 19.)
    - Goodman, Charles Austin (father) – death – condolences, February 1972 (Box 3, Folder 20.)
    - Goodman, Charles Austin (father) – death – condolences, February 1972 (Box 3, Folder 21.)
    - Goodman, Charles Austin (father) – death – condolences, February 1972 (Box 3, Folder 22.)
    - Goodman, Charlie (brother) (Box 3, Folder 23.)
  - Family
    - Goodman, Frances, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 1.)
    - Goodman, Greg (son) (Box 4, Folder 2.)
    - Goodman, Jeffrey J. (son) – Resume (Box 4, Folder 3.)
    - Goodman, John (son) (Box 4, Folder 4.)
    - Goodman, Julie (Mrs. Ken Koerner) (daughter) (Box 4, Folder 5.)
    - Correspondence from other relatives (Box 4, Folder 6.)
  - Kentucky Files
    - Correspondence, 1962 – 1972 (Box 4, Folder 7.)
    - Correspondence, 1976 - 1977 (Box 4, Folder 8.)
    - Correspondence, 1978 – 1980 (Box 4, Folder 9.)
    - Correspondence, 1982 – 1989 (Box 4, Folder 10.)
    - Baron Reunion, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 11.)
    - Brown, Governor John Y., 1980 (Box 4, Folder 12.)
    - Citizens Bank and Trust Company – History, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 13.)
    - Glasgow High School, Class of 1939, 50th Reunion, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 14.)
    - Glasgow magazine, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 15.)
    - Fountain Run Cemetery – History, 1855 -1955 (Box 4, Folder 16.)
    - Helms, Harold H. (Box 4, Folder 17.)
    - Kentucky Derby, May 4, 1963; ticket stubs (Box 4, Folder 18.)
    - Lindsey Wilson College, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 19.)
    - Pearce, John Ed (journalist) (Box 4, Folder 20.)
    - Vaughan, William W., 1966 – 1969 (Box 4, Folder 21.)
    - Vaughan, William W., 1970 – 1973 (Box 4, Folder 22.)
    - Vaughan, William W., 1974 (Box 4, Folder 23.)
    - Vaughan, William W., 1978;1991 (Box 4, Folder 24.)
    - Vaughan, William W., typescript of book on Alben Barkley (photocopy) (Box 4, Folder 25.)
    - Vaughan, William W., typescript of book on Alben Barkley (photocopy, pp. 65-132) (Box 4, Folder 26.)
    - Vaughan, William W. – typescript of book on Alben Barkley (photocopy) (Box 4, Folder 27.)
  - Kentucky Files
    - Watson, Thomas T. – last will and testament (Box 5, Folder 1.)
    - Western Kentucky State College – Class of 1943 – alumni (Box 5, Folder 2.)
    - Western Kentucky University (Box 5, Folder 3.)
    - Western Kentucky University – Julian Goodman Fund, 1981 -82 (Box 5, Folder 4.)
    - Western Kentucky University – Downing, Dero (Box 5, Folder 5.)
    - New articles (Box 5, Folder 6.)
  - People
    - Adams, Valda L., Jr. – obituary, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 7.)
    - Bowling, James C. (Box 5, Folder 8.)
    - Breathitt, Frances Holloman, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 9.)
    - Deeb, Gary, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 10.)
    - Foley, Dr. William T. (Box 5, Folder 11.)
    - Gagliardi, Frank (Larchmont, Winged Foot Golf Club) (Box 5, Folder 12.)
    - Goad, Rex (Box 5, Folder 13.)
    - Murray, George F., 1981 (Box 5, Folder 14.)
    - Porter, Paul A. (Box 5, Folder 15.)
    - Washburn, Abbott, 1987-88 (Box 5, Folder 16.)
    - Wood, Robert J., 1989 (Box 5, Folder 17.)
    - Resumes – Madeline David; Melanie Jamgochian; Dee Wedemeyer; others (Box 5, Folder 18.)
  - Other
    - Biographies of JG (Box 5, Folder 19.)
    - Birth certificate/radiophone program – May 1, 1922 – presented by NBC (Box 5, Folder 20.)
    - Birthday (Box 5, Folder 21.)
    - Book project material (Box 5, Folder 22.)
    - Cartoons/humor (Box 5, Folder 23.)
    - Cartoons/humor (Box 5, Folder 24.)
    - Quoque – the Hamptons, N.Y. (Box 5, Folder 25.)
    - Stationery, business cards (Box 5, Folder 26.)
    - Travel – Rome, Athens, October 1971 (Box 5, Folder 27.)
    - Travel, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 28.)
    - Travel – collection of postcards (Box 5, Folder 29.)
    - Miscellaneous – pages from appointment books, 1982 -1984 (Box 5, Folder 30.)
    - Miscellaneous – address change, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 31.)
    - Miscellaneous – newspaper articles (Box 5, Folder 32.)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 33.)
- Articles/Congressional Testimonies/Speeches by JG
  - Articles by Julian Goodman
    - “The Challenges of Broadcast Journalism” in The Quill, vol. 51, no. 10/with related material, October 1963 (Box 6, Folder 1.)
    - “Network TV Programming” in GW:The George Washington University Magazine/ with related material, Summer 1966 (Box 6, Folder 2.)
    - By-Liner for The Daily Variety, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 3.)
    - “The Call Board” in The Long Island Entertainer, Vol. 4, no. 36, August 19 – 26, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 4.)
    - “Television Digest White Paper Interview” vol. 7:11, March 13, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 5.)
    - comments for World Communication Day/ with related materials, May 7, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 6.)
    - comments for The Broadcasting Journal/ with related materials, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 7.)
    - requests for articles, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 8.)
    - “The Call Board” in The Long Island Entertainer, Vol.6, no.5, January 5 – 11, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 9.)
    - “Outlook for Commercial Broadcasting” drafts with related materials, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 10.)
    - “Television” (p. 24) in The American Way, February 1970 (Box 6, Folder 11.)
    - “TV Formulas Won’t Bring Fairness” in The Wall Street Journal/ with related materials, August 3, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 12.)
    - request for articles, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 13.)
    - “A Broadcaster Looks at Broadcasting” in Electronic Age Quarterly Publication of RCA, Spring 1971 (Box 6, Folder 14.)
    - “Commercials Against Commercials? Help!” in The New York Times/ with related materials, December 24, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 15.)
    - Outlook Section of the Pasadena Star News/ with related materials, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 16.)
    - “The Stake is Freedom” in Television Quarterly, Vol. x, no. 3/with related materials, Spring 1973 (Box 6, Folder 17.)
    - “They Thought They Heard a Tenor” in The Educational ABC’s of American Industry- draft with related materials, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 18.)
    - “The Future Depends on Guidelines Now” in Newsday, August 6, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 19.)
    - “Regulate, Punish, Control” in St. Louis Post-Dispatch, August 7, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 20.)
    - “It’s Everybody’s Freedom” in Television Quarterly, Vol. xi, no. 4, Summer 1974 (Box 6, Folder 21.)
    - “Fairness Doctrine – Fair or Foul?” in The Deadliner, Vol. 18, no. 3/ with related materials, July 1975 (Box 6, Folder 22.)
    - “What Communication Means to Me” for Cuadernos de Comunicacion/ with related materials, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 23.)
    - interview with JG and Herb Schlosser for the June 21, 1976 issue of Broadcasting Magazine/ with related materials, June 10, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 24.)
    - “Network News: Running Shackled?’ in Television Quarterly, Vol.xv, no. iii, Fall 1978 (Box 6, Folder 25.)
    - “Television Digest White Paper” interview, vol. 19:20 – full text and related materials, May 14, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 26.)
    - Review in Television/Radio Age of Making It Perfectly Clear: An Inside Account of Nixon’s Love-Hate Relationship with the Media by Herb Klein, October 20, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 27.)
    - “Viewpoints” in Television/Radio Age, March 3, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 28.)
    - – Review of The General in Television/Radio Age, February 2, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 29.)
    - – Guest columnist in USA Today, July 15, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 30.)
    - “No Compromise on ‘Fairness’” in Washington Journalism Review, November 1988 (Box 6, Folder 31.)
    - “The Olympics: a Better Way” in Washington Journalism Review, October 1988 (Box 6, Folder 32.)
    - “Networks are Thread Tying USA Together” in USA Today, Undated (Box 6, Folder 33.)
  - Congressional Testimony
    - August 23, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 1.)
    - October 9 – 16, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 2.)
    - June 3, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 3.)
    - June 10, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 4.)
    - October 12, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 5.)
    - March 23, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 6.)
    - March 9, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 7.)
    - March 22, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 8.)
    - March 7, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 9.)
    - April 5, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 10.)
    - April 29, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 11.)
    - April 29, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 12.)
    - June 11, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 13.)
    - July 30, 1976 (Staff paper) (Box 7, Folder 14.)
    - June 22, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 15.)
    - April 14, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 16.)
    - April 14 – 15, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 17.)
    - April 14 – 15, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 18.)
  - Congressional Testimony
    - April 14 - 15, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 1.)
    - April 28 - 30, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 2.)
    - Index, August 23, 1966 - February 28, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 3.)
  - Speeches
    - 1959 (Box 8, Folder 4.)
    - Pre-1963 – New Orleans (Box 8, Folder 5.)
    - South Carolina Broadcasters’ Association – Text, Correspondence, January 18, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 6.)
    - Radio TV Banquet, Indiana University, Bloomington, May 3, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 7.)
    - Annenberg School of Communication at University of Pennsylvania - 9. 1963 - Speech material, October 11, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 8.)
    - Association for Professional Broadcasting Education, Chicago, April 5, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 10.)
    - Address to Affiliates meeting, June 2, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 11.)
    - Advertising Club, Louisville, Kentucky – Text, Correspondence, September 11, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 12.)
    - Sigma Delta Chi, Kansas City, Missouri, December 3, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 13.)
    - University of Kentucky, Centennial Communications Symposium – Correspondence and Press Release, February 5, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 14.)
    - Sigma Delta Chi, Detroit, Michigan – Text and Correspondence, April 21, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 15.)
    - Military Chaplains Association, Boston, Massachusetts – Text and Correspondence, April 27, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 16.)
    - Fair Campaign Practices Committee, Washington DC -Correspondence, October 13, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 17.)
    - AFL Owners (American Football League), Houston, Texas, January 16, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 18.)
    - TV Affiliates, Honolulu, Hawaii, May 12, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 19.)
    - Commencement Address at Newport Schools for Girls, Newport, Rhode Island – Text and Correspondence, June 4, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 20.)